

Personal Details

No 5 cemetery road GRA enugu,

Nigerian

09034288174

ihuchiomajf@gmail.com

Date of Birth

29th May 1996

Skills

Time Management

Ability to work in a team

Adaptability

Laboratory Skills

Communication Skills

Microsoft Office

Hobbies

Watching Movies, Socializing with People, Shopping.

Languages

English Language

Igbo

Profile

A Passionate individual who is willing to contribute and make impact with the knowledge and experience acquired from previous jobs and to attain a high level of professionalism in my career and to acquire necessary knowledge in my field of study.

Employment History

Sales Personnel - Elchee Industries, Enugu

January 2016 – September 2016

- Managing and tracking sales records,
- Product Distribution at the department of sales and distribution.

Medical Laboratory Scientist (Lab Posting), Sango-Otta Ogun State

May 2018 – August 2018

• Worked at a state hospital in ogun state

Medical Laboratory Scientist (Lab Posting), Ogun State, Abeokuta

May 2019 – August 2019

• Worked at federal medical center abeokuta, ogun state.

Education

Naowa Group of Schools (Primary), Enugu Abakaliki

January 2004 – January 2007

Daughters of Divine Love Juniorate, Enugu

January 2007 – January 2012

Babcock University, Illishan Remo Ogun State

September 2014 – June 2020



IHUOMACHI CHIOMA OSUNKA

Personal Details

No 5 cemetery road GRA enugu,

Nigerian

09034288174

ihuchiomajf@gmail.com

Date of Birth

29th May 1996

Skills

Time Management

Ability to work in a team

Adaptability

Laboratory Skills

Communication Skills

Microsoft Office

Hobbies

Watching Movies, Socializing with People, Shopping.

Languages

English Language

Igbo

Certifications

- Certified in Emotional Competence and Empowerment.
- Certified in Word, Excel Customer Relationship
 Management and Project Management and Ms Project
- Certificate of PSENSE Employability Skills

References

Mr Enitan Seyi Samson from Babcock University

+234 905 280 1423

Dr John Ochei from Babcock University

+234 813 059 6145